JOAQUIN SOZA GUERRA

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 4+ years of related experience.

WORK HISTORY

Full Stack Developer, 11/2021 to 04/2022 Blockchain DApp - Santiago, Chile

 Currently i've been working with a team in a Blockchain DApp in the Avalanche network (React, Nodejs, Typescript, Solidity, Docker)

Full Stack Developer / Engineer, 04/2021 to 11/2021 Alpha Spa - Santiago, Chile

 We were a two man team, we built a platform for them in Python, Django, AWS, WordPress(Landing page)

Web Developer /Infrastructure, 11/2019 to 01/2021 Big Oak Spa - Santiago, Chile

 Multiple ecommerce were made with WordPress and some plugins were edited, also NAS systems were installed in the office. one men team.

EDUCATION

No Degree, Engineering in Computing And Informatics, 03/2018 Universidad Mayor - Santiago, Chile

High School Diploma, 12/2017

Colegio Santo Domingo - Santiago, Chile

PERSONAL INFORMATION

RUN: 19.957.470-1

Birth Date: June 12, 1998 Nationality: Chilean

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

I'm a self taught Full Stack Developer, I've been learning programming languages since i was 14 years old and using Linux since then. Also got a lot of experience with soldering and microcontrollers

CONTACT

Address: Plymouth PL5 1DH **Phone:** (+44) 7342336253

Email: contact@joaquinsoza.dev

WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

- · joaquinsoza.dev
- · linkedin.com/in/joaquinsoza/
- · github.com/joaquinsoza

SKILLS

- · Self-motivated professional
- · Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS
- · Version Control Systems: Git, GitHub
- Programming Languages: Python, JavaScript, C#, Solidity, TypeScript
- Frameworks: React, Vue, Django
- · Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, MariaDB
- · Cloud: AWS, DigitalOcean
- · Others: Docker, Node.js
- · Advanced Linux user

CERTIFICATIONS

- Full Stack Engineer, Codecademy 2021
- Solidity/Blockchain, Dapp University 2021
- · React, Codecademy 2020-2021
- HTML & CSS, Codecademy 2019

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native language

English:

C1

Advanced